CLARE SHIN

425.442.3399
Bellevue, WA
Haeyin.shin@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/clareshin github.com/haeyin haeyin.github.io

SUMMARY

Software and web development engineer specializing in media design and digital trends. Detail-oriented, I enjoy problem-solving from unique angles. Highly adaptable, I like to collaborate with others. I recognize when to take direction and when to self-start, and when to tailor to specifications and improvise. Fluent in Korean.

SKILLS SUMMARY

Programming: C#, Python, JS, HTML, CSS, SQL Frameworks: .NET, EF, Bootstrap, Angular Paradigms: MVC, Web Forms, Single Page, Cloud: Amazon Web Service (AWS), MS Azure

DB: Microsoft SQL Server, MySQL

Creative: Photoshop, Premiere, After Effects

OS: Windows XP-10, Mac OS X, Android, iOS IDE: Visual Studio, Brackets VCS: Microsoft Azure DevOps, GitHub Methodology: Agile/SCRUM Business Domains: Extended Reality,

Health, Education, Marketing

PROGRAMMING EXPERIENCE

- ASP.NET MVC Worked on a team to develop a web application for a client. Used Azure DevOps as VCS
 and adjusted the database for back end issues as well as dealt with front end technologies like UI/UX
 aspects.
- **Database First MVC** Developed an MVC web application that took a user's information and generated car insurance quotes that admin could later review.
- **SQL Server** Made a relational database from a data model for a library system that catalogues borrowers, books, authors, publishers, as well as branches and their inventories.
- HTML/XML Worked with markup languages to code pages with CSS to style them more comprehensively.
- JavaScript/JQuery Created an interactive tic-tac-toe game.
- General Incorporated a variety of coding languages (HTML5/CSS/JS/JQuery) to make a portfolio website.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER - Prosper IT Consulting

01/2020 - 06/2020 - Remote

- Work in a team to develop a complex multi-page website that takes login info and separates users into admin and subscriber using C#, Razor, JQuery, .NET, and SQL programming with an MVC paradigm.
- Debug and troubleshoot errors through unit testing.
- Utilize Azure DevOps, Slack, and Google Meet to execute Agile/SCRUM methodology within team.

EXECUTIVE MANAGER - Zengalt Inc

12/2018 - 09/2019 - Renton, WA

- Alpha testing for applications to be used for HoloLens.
- Support business analysis and development by market research and pursuing clientele and partners.
- Maintain team documents, backups, and records on Cloud and Azure Sharepoint.
- Pitch ideas for potential Mixed Reality projects and edit promotional videos.

FRONT DESK ADMINISTRATOR - Uniclinic PLLC

03/2018 - 12/2018 - Renton, WA

- Perform all front desk operations including reception.
- Schedule and bill patients, calling to remind them of upcoming appointments.
- Make and organize patient charts.

LEAP MENTOR - Cheng Yin Private Academy

07/2016 - 04/2018 - Remote

- Provide students with essay feedback, interviews, and general or specialized advice.
- Conduct student mock interviews and help improve their verbal communication skills.

• Keep in close contact with students via Skype and email.

EDUCATION/CERTIFICATES

THE TECH ACADEMY – Certificate in C# & .NET

2019 - 2020 - Remote

Framework

Coding bootcamp teaching computer science and software development via hands-on training. Nearly 1,000 hours divided into many courses and subjects: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Database and SQL, C#, version control, and even project management.

Assortment of projects completed, including object-oriented-programming, data modeling, web API, MVC, Entity Framework, and a sprint for a Live Project on Azure DevOps in an Agile/SCRUM environment.

NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - Tisch School of Arts

2009 -2015 - New York, NY

B.F.A. in Undergraduate Film & TV

Honors: Trustee Scholarship; Honors Scholar

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

2020